

CONTACTS

- +250 780 770 311
- manizabayopatience08@ gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/patience-m/
- Kigali-Nyarugenge-Rwanda KN 108 St

SKILLS

- Computer Literacy
- Conducting EIA
- GIS Based Data Collection
- Data Entry & Analysis
- GIS-Mapping
- Technical Support
- Team Spirit
- Leadership

INTRESTS

- Environmental Research and Compliance
- Food Resilence and Security
- Graphic Designing
- Reading

LANGUAGES

• English (fluent)

PATIENCE MANIZABAYO

Emvironmental Planner

I am an environmentalist dedicated to integrating the principles of environmental planning and management with a keen focus on socioeconomic considerations. My expertise lies in creating a harmonious balance between developmental needs and environmental sustainability accompained with GIS-mapping. I am a dedicated and proactive motivated worker known for my strong work ethic, and adaptability. With good communication skills, I collaborate seamlessly within teams and excel in independent tasks. My consistent ability to meet deadlines showcases my time management and organizational abilities. I am a quick learner who embraces challenges, and my commitment to continuous improvement drives me to contribute effectively to any work environment.

EDUCATION

E.S ST JOSEPH KARUGANDA

2016 - 2018: Advanced Level Certificate in Mathematics, Economics and Geography

UNIVERSITY OF RWANDA-CST

2019-2023: BCs (Hons) in Geography: Environmental Planning

EXPERIENCE

2021-2023 CHURCH DIGITAL DEPARTMENT ASSISSTANT

• I have served Digital and Technical Assistance in Adventist Students Association / University of Rwanda

2023: LAND USE PLANNING & MANAGEMENT

 Industrial Attachment: Land Use Planning & Management and Land related serives at Nyarugenge Sector/City of Kigali

2023: DISASTERS ASSESSMENT & MAPPING

 Project: Flood Vulnerability Assessment Using GIS. Case study of Mpazi Sub-Catchment

LEADERSHIP

2021-2023: VOLUNTIERRING

 Commissioner of Mobilization in RYVCP/ University of Rwanda/College of Science and Technology

REFERENCE

Dr. Ernest Uwayezu

Lecturer / University of Rwanda Phone: (+250)783 022 510 Email: wayezuernest@gmail.com

Mr. Hyacinthe Ngwijabagabo

Assisstant Lecturer / University of Rwanda (+250) 785 550 875